CHRISTOPHER SHOCKLEY **SOFTWARE DEVELOPER**

Summary

Software Developer with a customer service and military background. Focused on producing products that fulfill the needs of the user, investors and fellow developers. Committed to growing as a developer and a human being.

Projects

The Mentor Connector - Front End Developer

GitHub

React | Redux | Node/Express | Material-UI | PostgreSQL

A social media site where soon to be graduates can connect with mentors within their same field, or same institution.

- Collaborated remotely on a 5 person team.
- Wrote code for registration authentication.
- · Worked on State Management using Redux
- Gained an understanding of working with different skill levels and personalities.

Strainiac - Back End Developer

A application where the user can search for which strain is best for their various ailments. using data science and machine learning.

React | Node | Express

- Built backend API
- Authentication Setup
- Login/Register Setup

Conway's Game of Life - React Developer

A cellular automation created by British Mathematician John Horton Conway.

React

- Using React I build Conway's classic game.
- Built responsive, with options to change the game around
- · Custom algorithm used.

Employment

Starbucks · Barista Shift Supervisor

South Euclid, OH · July 2018 to Jan. 2021

Manage customer relations and barista at busy drive-thru store

Viking Outfitters · Team Lead

Cleveland, OH · Aug. 2013 to Mar. 2017

Textbook management, organization and inventory

East Cleveland Public Library · Assistant Network Administrator

East Cleveland, OH · Feb. 2007 to Jan. 2010

Maintained network of public and employee stations

May 1999 to Jan. 2005

US Navy · Fire Control Technician

Gained UNIX experience Worked in small teams

♥ Cleveland, OH

\(7575975810

Contact

in christopherishockley/

cishockleysr@gmail.com

C cishocksr

Education

Lambda School July 2019 to Jan. 2021

Full Stack Web Developer Track

Use Agile Software Development

Management

Including Frontend, Backend, and Computer Science

Skills

Javascript

HTML/CSS

React

Redux

NodeJS

Express Python

JEST

React Testing Library

SOL

Knex